trustedopinion.com 2009-04-11

# Privacy Policy - Trusted Opinion™ Great Recommendations and Reviews

Effective date: July 17, 2006 

## 1\. We know you value your privacy

You take your privacy seriously and Trusted Opinion strives to meet your expectations relating to how we collect, use and make available personal information you provide to us. 

## 2\. Consent to privacy policy

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices which govern Trusted Opinion's collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. The Policy pertains to the use of [http://www.trustedopinion.com](http://www.trustedopinion.com/) and the Trusted Opinion service (the "Service"). By using Trusted Opinion or visiting the website, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information pursuant to the terms of the Privacy Policy. 

## 3\. Information collected

Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, your name, home address, telephone number, email address, and credit card information. We require the following personal information from you during the Trusted Opinion registration process: name, email, zip code, country and gender. To provide you with better search results, you can optionally provide us further information about yourself such as age, occupation and marital status. You also have the option of uploading a picture or image of yourself for use on your profile. 

You may provide the email addresses of your friends that you would like to invite into your Trusted Opinion network. We do not sell, share or disclose your friends' email addresses with any third parties except as with any of the personal information you provide to us, this information may be accessible to our vendors and suppliers under limited circumstances. 

Requests and messages that you send within the Trusted Opinion system are stored on our system only for your own records, and not used for any other purpose. We collect email and feedback that you send to Trusted Opinion for administrative purposes. 

In addition, we automatically collect non-personal information such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser data (such as your browser type) and site referral information. We use internet "cookies" to set and remember your browsing preferences, sign-in information and view your browsing patterns, such as what links are clicked, which profiles & reviews are most popular and what pages are viewed. Cookies are small text files downloaded onto your computer which store your information for following visits. 

## 4\. Children

Trusted Opinion is not intended for children under the age of 13, and by using the Service you attest that you are not under the age of 13. We do not collect personal information from children under the age of 13 and if we learn we have such information we will promptly delete it. 

## 5\. Use of information 

Trusted Opinion uses your personal information to allow you to register, sign in and use Trusted Opinion, and to process your email, invite or review requests and to render our services to you. We may use your reviews and feedback together with your first name and last name initial for promotional and marketing purposes on our website and elsewhere. We will only use your photo with your express permission. Aggregate information that does not identify you may be used for marketing or business purposes. 

With your express consent, we may use your personal information to send you special offers or information from our trusted business partners. You may choose to not receive these offers by opting out in your profile page. We may use your personal information for internal purposes and to send you technical or administrative email notifications. 

Browser information, IP addresses, and cookie information are used to better tailor our content to site users' needs. Cookies are used to let you sign in, remember your browsing preferences, view browsing patterns and to show you appropriate advertisements. See above for further information about cookies. 

**Security of your Information**

We take the security of your personal information seriously. Your account information is password-protected and Trusted Opinion protects data transmissions by using SSL-encryption. 

We limit access to your personal information to employees and service providers who need access in order to do their jobs. We contractually require our service providers to have the same high privacy standards as we do. 

Although we use every precaution to protect our users' personal information, we cannot guarantee that your data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure and that our privacy safeguards will not be breached. By using this web site or providing personal information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of this site. Trusted Opinion may post a notice on our web site if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to view the TrustedOpinion.com web site. Trusted Opinion may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach, you should notify us at [privacy@trustedopinion.com](mailto:privacy@trustedopinion.com). 

## 6\. Sharing of Information

Trusted Opinion will only share your personal information according to our Privacy Policy. Trusted Opinion does not rent, sell or share your personal information with non-affiliated third parties for their direct marketing purposes without your consent. We share personal information in the following situations: 

**During your Use of Trusted Opinion**

As a registered Trusted Opinion user, you decide how much information you want to disclose in your profile. By default, your full name and your email address are only shown to your 1st Circle Friends. 1st Circle Friends are the Friends that you invite into your network, or where you accept an invitation to join a network. Your photo, website and blog links, all of which are optional, are by default shown to all users in your extended network. 

You can change the privacy setting for your name, email address, photo, website and blog at any time by going to your "My Account" section and selecting "Show only to 1st Circle Friends" or "Show to All" in your extended network from the drop down boxes. Friends in your extended network will only be able to view the information you decide to make public and your reviews. 

You can search for users who are not in your extended network by their email address. If there is a match we will disclose the user's information according to their preferred privacy settings in "My Account" as described above. You can then send an invitation to your network to that user. If you select "Show to All" in your privacy settings, other users will be able to see your information if they search for you by email address. 

When you upload your friends' email addresses into the Service, we will only use these email addresses to connect you with other users or to allow you to invite your friends to use Trusted Opinion. We will not disclose these email addresses to any third parties or business partners for marketing purposes. 

**To Third Party Partners**

We may use cookies by third party partners to help analyze and optimize our online traffic and to display advertisements. We control how this data may and may not be used by our partners. 

We may share aggregate information that does not identify you with our business partners or advertisers. If you expressly consent, we may share your personal information with business partners that may offer services we believe may be of interest to you. You can control whether you would like to receive offers from our business partners through your profile page. 

**For Administrative and Legal Purposes**

Trusted Opinion may disclose your personal information to carry out a user's request, or where Trusted Opinion reasonably believes that doing so is in compliance with our legal obligations pursuant to a search warrant or subpoena, or is in Trusted Opinion's interest to protect its property or other legal rights or the rights or property of others. We may also disclose your personal information where Trusted Opinion reasonably believes it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, including without limitation, fraud, violations of Trusted Opinion's Terms of Service, or as otherwise permitted or required by law. 

Staff or third party suppliers or vendors of Trusted Opinion may access your personal information to assist Trusted Opinion in operating its business. We require our vendors to have the same standard of privacy protections as we do. 

**Merger or Bankruptcy**

In the event of a bankruptcy, sale of assets, transfer of ownership, acquisition or merger of Trusted Opinion, we may be required to disclose or transfer your information to any prospective or acquiring party. We will notify you by email of any such transfer and in such circumstances your personal information shall be treated as would any other asset of Trusted Opinion 

**Links to Other Websites**

Trusted Opinion provides hyperlinks to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any linked websites and we expressly disclaim any liability relating to their activities or privacy practices. 

## 7\. Control of Your Personal Information

You have control over how much personal information you reveal to other users in your network. Most of the personal information that we ask for in your profile is optional. You can delete or modify information from your profile at any time. 

You can close your Trusted Opinion account by emailing us an account deletion request at [feedback@trustedopinion.com](mailto:feedback@trustedopinion.com). Please include your full name, email address and user name in your request. However, please note that your identification and contact information may remain in our records for some period. 

## 8\. International Visitors

Trusted Opinion is designed for U.S. users and complies with U.S. privacy laws. If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing personal information that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personal information to the United States and by providing your personal information to us you consent to that transfer. 

## 9\. Changes to the Privacy Policy

Trusted Opinion may update this Privacy Policy. Changes will be indicated by a change to the effective date at the start of the policy. For changes to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing the change. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the Personal Information we collect. Your continued use of this web site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates. 

## 10\. Contact us

If you have any questions relation to our privacy practices, this policy or your personal information, please contact us by email at [privacy@trustedopinion.com](mailto:privacy@trustedopinion.com). 

**Postal Mail Address:**

Trusted Opinion Inc.  
c/o Wilson Sonsini Goodrich & Rosati  
Palo Alto Headquarters  
650 Page Mill Road  
Palo Alto, CA, USAlifornia 94304-1050  
Phone | 650-493-9300  
Fax | 650-493-6811

Attention: Craig N. Lang
